Broadcast Center Recordings, circa 1980-2017: Finding Aid AC362
University Archives
- Series 5: Broadcast Center Recordings, 2010 January 9-2012 December 19; 20 boxes
  - Commencement 2010, 2010 June 01; 1537; 1 box (Box 63)
  - Walter F. Murphy Memorial Service, 2010 June 09; 1538; 1 box (Box 63)
  - ABOTA Mock Trial, 2010 June 10; 1539; 1 box (Box 63)
  - ABOTA Mock Trial, 2010 June 10; 1540; 1 box (Box 63)
  - ABOTA Mock Trial, 2010 June 10; 1541; 1 box (Box 63)
  - ABOTA Mock Trial, 2010 June 10; 1542; 1 box (Box 63)
    Tape 4; Conference and Event Services
  - Graduate School Open House, 2010 June 25; 1544; 1 box (Box 63)
    Tape #1 Morning Session; Office of Academic Affairs and Diversity
  - Graduate School Open House, 2010 June 25; 1545; 1 box (Box 63)
    Tape #2 Graduate Student Panel; Office of Academic Affairs and Diversity
  - Tikvah Project - Panel - Sex and Family`, 2010 August 05; 1623; 1 box (Box 63)
  - Tikvah Project - Panel - War and Morality, 2010 August 03; 1623; 1 box (Box 63)
  - Yenor Lecture, 2011 April 11; 1733; 1 box (Box 63)
  - Czeslaw Milosz, 2011 November 05; 1915; 1 box (Box 63)
    Belknap Visitor
  - The Future of Nuclear Power, 2011 November 10; 1977; 1 box (Box 63)
    Fall 2011 Maclean House Lectures: The Future of Nuclear Power: Climate Change, Nuclear Power and Nuclear Proliferation: Magnitude Matters; Alumni Association
  - Excerpt from the Eighth Public Affairs Forum, 2011 May 06; 1978; 1 box (Box 63)
    Excerpt from the Eighth Public Affairs Forum; Alumni Association
  - Communication Officer and Supervisor Training, 2011 October 04; 1979; 1 box (Box 63)
  - JRC Annual Conference Day 2, 2012 February 20; 2353; 1 box (Box 73)
    1/2 Day Bowl 016 Robertson Hall; WWS/Undergraduate Program and Other
  - Alexander Glaser, 2010 April 12; 2093; 1 box (Box 63)
    Balancing Risks: Nuclear Energy and Climate Change
  - Michael Oppenheimer, 2010 February 01; 2097; 1 box (Box 64)
    Copenhagen: The Sound and the Fury Signifying...
  - James Madison Program, 2012 April 13; 2101; 1 box (Box 64)
    Governing Science: (Part 1- Science and the Evolution of Man)Technical Progress, Ethical Norms, and Democracy; Politics
  - James Madison Program, 2012 April 13; 2102; 1 box (Box 64)
    Governing Science: (Part 2- Science and the Reduction of Man)Technical Progress, Ethical Norms, and Democracy; Politics
  - James Madison Program, 2012 April 13; 2103; 1 box (Box 64)
    Governing Science: (Part 3- The Abuse of Science)Technical Progress, Ethical Norms, and Democracy; Politics
  - James Madison Program, 2012 April 14; 2104; 1 box (Box 64)
    Governing Science: (Part 4- What are Limits?) Technical Progress, Ethical Norms, and Democracy; Politics
  - James Madison Program, 2012 April 14; 2105; 1 box (Box 64)
    Governing Science: (Part 5- Governing Science in a Democracy Republic)Technical Progress, Ethical Norms, and Democracy; Politics
  - James Madison Program, 2012 April 14; 2106; 1 box (Box 64)
    Governing Science: (Part 6-Keeping Scientific Enterprise Vibrant and Ethical)Technical Progress, Ethical Norms, and Democracy; Politics
  - Steven Mayer, 2011 September 02; 2107; 1 box (Box 64)
    Steven Mayer
  - James Madison Program, 2012 May 21; 2108; 1 box (Box 64)
    ASFI conference, Part 1 Key note address-James Ceasar; Politics
  - James Madison Program, 2012 May 21; 2109; 1 box (Box 64)
    ASFI conference, Part 2 Progressivism and Institutional Change; Politics
  - James Madison Program, 2012 May 21; 2110; 1 box (Box 64)
    ASFI Conference, Part 3 The Election of 1912; Politics
  - James Madison Program, 2012 May 22; 2111; 1 box (Box 64)
    ASFI Conference, Part 4 The Legacy of Progressivism in Contemporary American Politics...; Politics
  - James Madison Program, 2012 May 22; 2112; 1 box (Box 64)
    ASFI Conference, Part 5 American Law and the Legacy of Progressivism; Politics
  - James Madison Program, 2012 May 22; 2113; 1 box (Box 64)
    ASFI Conference, Part 6 Progressivism and the American Founding; Politics
  - James Madison Program, 2012 June 01; 2114; 1 box (Box 64)
    American Politics and America's Future: Are We at a Crossroads?; Politics
  - Charles Forsberg, 2010 March 29; 2115; 1 box (Box 64)
    Is Nuclear Energy the Enabling Technology for Large-Scale Renewables
  - Ronald Bailey, 2010 March 08; 2118; 1 box (Box 64)
    Freedom versus Bioethics
  - Kelly Sims Gallagher, 2010 February 08; 2120; 1 box (Box 65)
    Breaking the Impasse Between the United States and China on Climate Change
  - Marvin Miller, 2010 April 05; 2121; 1 box (Box 65)
    In Hiroshima's Shadow: Prospects for Global Nuclear Disarmament -Then and Now
  - Ana Arrolo, 2010 September 19; 2122; 1 box (Box 65)
    International Cooperation to Strengthen SandT Innovation in Developing Countries"
  - Claire Kremen, 2010 March 22; 2129; 1 box (Box 65)
    Diversifies Farming Systems: Benefits and Obstacles
  - Richard Moss, 2010 February 05; 2134; 1 box (Box 65)
    Bridging the Science-Society Divide: Developing Integrated Scenarios for Climate Change Decision Support
  - 2012 Questbridge Conference, 2012 June 16; 2136; 1 box (Box 65)
    Michael McCullough Pre-Med Discussion
  - Rebecca Mackinnon, 2012 March 29; 2137; 1 box (Box 65)
    Consent of the Networked: The Worldwide Struggle for Internet Freedom
  - 2012 Questbridge Conference, 2012 June 15; 2138; 1 box (Box 65)
  - 2012 Questbridge Conference, 2012 June 16; 2139; 1 box (Box 65)
    Michael McCullough Choosing the Right College
  - Carmen Reinhart, 2012 May 03; 2140; 1 box (Box 65)
  - Turing Centennial Celebration, 2012 May 10; 2158; 1 box (Box 66)
    10:00a-Dana Scott 11:00a-Philip Wadler
  - Turing Centennial Celebration, 2012 May 10; 2160; 1 box (Box 66)
    12:45p-Shirley Tilghman 1:00p-Les Valiant 2:00p-Andy Yao
  - Turing Centennial Celebration, 2012 May 10; 2161; 1 box (Box 66)
    3:30p-Robert Kahn 4:30p-Dick Karp
  - Turing Centennial Celebration part 1 and2, 2012 May 11; 2162; 1 box (Box 66)
    10:00a Martin Davis 11:00a James Murray
  - Turing Centennial Celebration, 2012 May 11; 2163; 1 box (Box 67)
    1:00p Barbara Liskov 2:00p Tom Mitchell
  - Turing Centennial Celebration, 2012 May 11; 2164; 1 box (Box 67)
    3:30p Andrew Odlyzko 4:30p Ron Rives
  - Turing Centennial Celebration, 2012 May 12; 2165; 1 box (Box 67)
    10:00a-David Harel, Weizmann Institute. Standing on the Shoulders of a Giant
  - Turing Centennial Celebration, 2012 May 12; 2166; 1 box (Box 67)
    11:00a-Avi Wigderson, IAS. The Hardness of Proving Computational Hardness
  - Turing Centennial Celebration, 2012 May 12; 2167; 1 box (Box 67)
    1:00p-Shafi Goldwasser, MIT and the Weizmann Institute. Pseudo Deterministic Algorithms
  - Turing Centennial Celebration, 2012 May 12; 2168; 1 box (Box 67)
    2:00p-Bob Tarjan, Princeton. Search Tree Mysteries
  - Turing Centennial Celebration, 2012 May 12; 2169; 1 box (Box 67)
    3:30p-Dick Lipton, Georgia Tech. What Would Turing Be Doing Today?
  - Turing Centennial Celebration, 2012 May 12; 2170; 1 box (Box 67)
    4:30p-Christos Papadimitriou, Berkeley. The Origin of Computable Numbers
  - S.A.F.E., 2012 July 12; 2171; 1 box (Box 67)
    Student Activities Funding Engine
  - "A Better Chance", 2012 June 24; 2172; 1 box (Box 67)
  - Portes Lecture, 2012 June 08; 2173; 1 box (Box 67)
    Professor Alejandro Portes
  - Griswold Dedication, 2012 May 18; 2175; 1 box (Box 67)
  - Leadership Series-Ivy club, 2011 September 15; 2181; 1 box (Box 67)
    Professor Robert George
  - Leadership Series-Ivy Club, 2011 November 11; 2182; 1 box (Box 67)
    Charles Lowrey
  - Leadership Series-Ivy club, 2011 November 11; 2183; 1 box (Box 67)
    General Peter Pace
  - Leadership Series-Ivy Club, 2011 November 11; 2184; 1 box (Box 67)
    Governor Christie Whitman
  - Leadership Series-Ivy Club, 2011 November 11; 2185; 1 box (Box 67)
    Professor Emeritus John Fleming
  - Leadership Series-Ivy Club, 2011 November 11; 2186; 1 box (Box 67)
    Professor Charles O'Reilley
  - Leadership Series-Ivy Club, 2011 November 11; 2187; 1 box (Box 67)
    Ambassador Theodore Kattouf
  - Reflections on Diversity, 2012 September 11; 2188; 1 box (Box 68)
    Reflections on Diversity; Dean of Undergraduate Students
  - Freshman Orientation/Assembly, 2012 September 09; 2189; 1 box (Box 68)
    Ed Felton; Dean of the College
  - Toni Morrison Lectures, 2012 April 17; 2190; 1 box (Box 68)
    Bill T. Jones Part 1; Center for African American Studies
  - The Way You Move, 2012 September 12; 2191; 1 box (Box 68)
    Also known as Sex On A Saturday Night; Dean of Undergraduate Students
  - The Belief in Things Unseen, 2012 September 13; 2192; 1 box (Box 68)
    Frederick Douglass and the Constitutional Imagination; The Council of the Humanities
  - Dining Services Orientation Video, 2012 September 25; 2193; 1 box (Box 68)
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center Summer School on Combustion, 2012 June 25; 2194; 1 box (Box 68)
    Combustion Chemistry Hai Wang Day 1, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 25; 2195; 1 box (Box 68)
    Combustion Theory Heinz Pitsch Day 1, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 25; 2196; 1 box (Box 68)
    Combustion Theory Heinz Pitsch Day 1, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 25; 2197; 1 box (Box 68)
    Internal Combustion Timothy C. Lieuwen Day 1, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 25; 2198; 1 box (Box 68)
    Internal Combustion Timothy C. Lieuwen Day 1, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 25; 2199; 1 box (Box 68)
    Frontiers in Combustion Robert H. Socolow Day 1, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 25; 2200; 1 box (Box 68)
    Frontiers in Combustion Robert H. Socolow Day 1, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 26; 2201; 1 box (Box 68)
    Combustion Chemistry Hai Wang Day 2, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 26; 2202; 1 box (Box 68)
    Combustion Chemistry Hai Wang Day 2, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 26; 2203; 1 box (Box 68)
    Combustion Theory Heinz Pitsch Day 2, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 26; 2204; 1 box (Box 68)
    Combustion Theory Heinz Pitsch Day 2, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 26; 2205; 1 box (Box 68)
    Internal Combustion Timothy C. Lieuwen Day 2, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 26; 2206; 1 box (Box 68)
    Internal Combustion Timothy C. Lieuwen Day 2, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 26; 2207; 1 box (Box 68)
    Frontiers in Combustion Geo. A. Richards Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 26; 2208; 1 box (Box 68)
    Frontiers in Combustion Geo. A. Richards Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 27; 2209; 1 box (Box 68)
    Combustion Theory Heinz Pitsch Day 3, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 27; 2210; 1 box (Box 68)
    Combustion Theory Heinz Pitsch Day 3, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 27; 2211; 1 box (Box 69)
    Combustion Chemistry Hai Wang Day 3, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 27; 2212; 1 box (Box 69)
    Combustion Chemistry Hai Wang Day 3, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 25; 2213; 1 box (Box 69)
    Internal Combustion Rolf D. Reitz Day 1, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 25; 2214; 1 box (Box 69)
    Internal Combustion Rolf D. Reitz Day 1, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 27; 2215; 1 box (Box 69)
    Frontiers in Combustion William H. Green Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 27; 2216; 1 box (Box 69)
    Frontiers in Combustion William H. Green Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 28; 2217; 1 box (Box 69)
    Combustion Chemistry Hai Wang Day 4, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 28; 2218; 1 box (Box 69)
    Combustion Chemistry Hai Wang Day 4, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 28; 2219; 1 box (Box 69)
    Combustion Theory Heinz Pitsch Day 4, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 28; 2220; 1 box (Box 69)
    Combustion Theory Heinz Pitsch Day 4, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 26; 2221; 1 box (Box 69)
    Internal Combustion Roald D. Reitz Day 2, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 26; 2222; 1 box (Box 69)
    Internal Combustion Roald D. Reitz Day 2, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 28; 2223; 1 box (Box 69)
    Frontiers in Combustion Jacqueline H. Chen Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 28; 2224; 1 box (Box 69)
    Frontiers in Combustion Jacqueline H. Chen Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 28; 2225; 1 box (Box 69)
    Frontiers in Combustion Jacqueline H. Chen Part 3 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 29; 2226; 1 box (Box 69)
    Combustion Chemistry Hai Wang Day 5, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 29; 2227; 1 box (Box 69)
    Combustion Chemistry Hai Wang Day 5, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 29; 2228; 1 box (Box 69)
    Combustion Theory Heinz Pitsch Day 5, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 29; 2229; 1 box (Box 69)
    Combustion Theory Heinz Pitsch Day 5, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 27; 2230; 1 box (Box 69)
    Internal Combustion Rolf D. Reitz Day 3, Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 27; 2231; 1 box (Box 69)
    Internal Combustion Rolf D. Reitz Day 3, Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 29; 2232; 1 box (Box 69)
    Frontiers in Combustion Richard A. Yetter Part 1 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - Combustion Energy Frontier Research Center, 2012 June 29; 2233; 1 box (Box 69)
    Frontiers in Combustion Richard A. Yetter Part 2 CEFRC Summer School on Combustion June 25-29, 2012
  - "Constitutional moments" - Michael S. Greve, 2012 September 14; 2234; 1 box (Box 69)
    Michael Greve Lecture James Madison Program Lewis Library 120 (assigned to James Grassi); Politics
  - Tikvah, 2012 July 22; 2235; 1 box (Box 69)
    (LS) Tikvah Dodds Auditorium DVD 1/5; Conference and Event Services
  - Tikvah, 2012 July 25; 2236; 1 box (Box 70)
    (LS) Tikvah Project Lewis Library 120 DVD 2/5; Conference and Event Services
  - Tikvah, 2012 July 30; 2237; 1 box (Box 70)
    (LS) Tikvah Project Lewis Library 120 DVD 3/5; Conference and Event Services
  - Tikvah, 2012 August 05; 2238; 1 box (Box 70)
    (LS) Tikvah Project Lewis Library 120 DVD 4/5; Conference and Event Services
  - Tikvah, 2012 August 06; 2239; 1 box (Box 70)
    (LS) Tikvah Project Lewis Library 120 DVD 5/5; Conference and Event Services
  - Joyce Lee Malcolm Lecture, 2012 September 28; 2240; 1 box (Box 70)
    "Self Defense: Our Most Basic Right or a Danger to Public Safety? The Anglo-American Divide" - Joyce Lee Malcolm Lewis Library 120; Politics
  - Dava Sobel and Diane Ackerman Lecture, 2012 April 27; 2242; 1 box (Box 70)
    Public Lecture McCosh 50; Public Lectures
  - "Proposition 8 and the Distractions of Social Science" -Daniel Robinson, 2012 September 27; 2243; 1 box (Box 70)
    Proposition 8 and the Distractions of Social Science Daniel Robinson Lecture; Politics
  - Neural Dynamics of Cognitive Control, 2012 April 18; 2244; 1 box (Box 70)
    Speaker: Tim Buschman, Massachusetts Institute of Technology; Neuroscience
  - The Evolutionary "Design" of Proteins, 2012 April 12; 2245; 1 box (Box 70)
    Speaker: Rama Ranaganathan, UT Southwestern Medical Center; Chemistry
  - Career Services Overview Video, 2012 April 11; 2246; 1 box (Box 70)
    Career Services Overview Video
  - Confronting the Reality of Sexual Violence, 2012 September 28; 2247; 1 box (Box 70)
    David Lisak, PhD SHARE Program
  - Philanderfest, 2012 September 06; 2248; 1 box (Box 70)
    Dodds Auditorium Day 1, Part 1; Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences
  - Philanderfest, 2012 September 06; 2249; 1 box (Box 70)
    Day 1, Part 2 Dodds Auditorium; Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences
  - Philanderfest, 2012 September 06; 2250; 1 box (Box 70)
    Day 1, Part 3 Dodds Auditorium; Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences
  - Philanderfest, 2012 September 07; 2251; 1 box (Box 70)
    Day 2, Part 1 Dodds Auditorium; Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences
  - Philanderfest, 2012 September 07; 2252; 1 box (Box 70)
    Day 2, Part 2 Dodds Auditorium; Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences
  - Philanderfest, 2012 September 07; 2253; 1 box (Box 70)
    Day 2, Part 3 Dodds Auditorium; Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences
  - Minerva Lecture, 2012 October 10; 2254; 1 box (Box 70)
    McDonnell A01; Mathematics
  - Scruton Lecture, 2012 October 11; 2255; 1 box (Box 70)
  - Architectural Presentation Trustees Meeting, 2012 January 27; 2256; 1 box (Box 70)
    Architectural Presentation Trustees Meeting
  - Callaloo Conference - morning session, 2012 October 13; 2257; 1 box (Box 70)
    Callaloo Conference Morning session Dodds Auditorium; Center for African American Studies
  - Callaloo Conference - Afternoon Session, 2012 October 13; 2258; 1 box (Box 70)
    Callaloo Conference Afternoon Session Dodds Auditorium; Center for African American Studies
  - Signature Lecture - Michael Eric Dyson, 2012 October 09; 2260; 1 box (Box 70)
    Signature Lecture Michael Eric Dyson McCosh 10; Wilson College
  - Madhavi Sunder, 2012 October 17; 2261; 1 box (Box 71)
    CITP (Center for Information Technology Policy); Center for Information Technology Policy
  - Tiger Talk - Ginger Zakian, 2012 October 25; 2262; 1 box (Box 71)
    Speaker: Ginger Zakian
  - English Critical Encounters, 2012 October 04; 2264; 1 box (Box 71)
    Critical Encounters 106 McCormick; English
  - A Marine's Honor - Krauss Lecture, 2012 November 05; 2265; 1 box (Box 71)
    A Marine's Honor: The Supreme Court from Snyder to Alvarez Michael Krauss James Madison Program; Politics
  - Noam Chomsky Lecture, 2012 November 12; 2266; 1 box (Box 71)
    Noam Chomsky Lecture Location: 105 Computer Science; Council of the Humanities
  - Tanner Lectures - Part 1, 2012 October 17; 2267; 1 box (Box 71)
    Ian Morris Friend Center, Room 101; Center for Study of Human Values
  - Tanner Lectures - Part 2, 2012 October 18; 2268; 1 box (Box 71)
  - Jim Hamilton, 2010 November 19; 2269; 1 box (Box 71)
    Jim Hamilton Highlight Seminar Series
  - Opening Exercises, 2012 September 09; 2393; 1 box (Box 73)
    Opening Exercises for the Class of 2016
  - Peter R. Kann, 2012 September 21; 2397; 1 box (Box 73)
    Ivy Club Leadership Program; Other
  - Global Dialogue Jeremy Adelman, 2012 October 03; 2345; 1 box (Box 73)
    Global Dialogue Series Jeremy Adelman with Molly Greene and Anthony Grafton
  - EPICS Final Projects, 2012 December 12; 2398; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Obama or Romney: The First 100 Days, 2012 October 20; 2270; 1 box (Box 71)
    Obama or Romney: The First 100 Days Fall Football Lecture Series
  - Tooth Tattoos and Other Biointerfaced Nanodevices, 2012 October 13; 2271; 1 box (Box 71)
    Fall Football Lecture Michael McAlpine
  - Adventures in the Theater, 2012 November 28; 2272; 1 box (Box 71)
    Conversation with David Binder and Karen Fricker 106 McCormick Hall; The Council of the Humanities
  - The IMAGINE Speaker Series - Maisha Walker, 2012 November 28; 2273; 1 box (Box 71)
    Maisha Walker 36 University Place; Career Services
  - Beyond Our Means: Why America Spends While the World Saves, 2012 November 17; 2274; 1 box (Box 71)
    Sheldon Garon Fall Football Lecture
  - David Brooks, 2012 November 26; 2275; 1 box (Box 71)
    NYT Columnist David Brooks Stafford Little Lecture McCosh 50
  - Canadian Studies Panel, 2012 December 06; 2276; 1 box (Box 71)
    Pierre McGuire and Blair Mackasey Dodds Auditorium; Alumni Council
  - The Online Revolution - Education for Everyone, 2012 October 17; 2277; 1 box (Box 71)
    Daphne Koller
  - Settler Colonialism: Then and Now, 2012 December 06; 2278; 1 box (Box 71)
    Mahmood Mamdani Settle Colonialism: Then and Now McCosh 10; English
  - Callaloo Conference Part 1A, 2012 October 12; 2279; 1 box (Box 71)
    McCosh 10 Panel Discussions - 9:00 am to 6:00 pm; Center for African American Studies
  - Callaloo Conference Part 1B, 2012 October 12; 2280; 1 box (Box 71)
  - Callaloo Conference Part 2, 2012 October 12; 2281; 1 box (Box 71)
  - Callaloo Conference Part 3, 2012 October 12; 2282; 1 box (Box 71)
  - Callaloo Conference Part 4, 2012 October 12; 2283; 1 box (Box 71)
    Callaloo Conference Part 4 McCosh 10 9am - 6pm
  - Global Dialogue Jeremy Adelman, 2012 October 17; 2346; 1 box (Box 73)
    Global Dialogue Series with Benjamon Elman
  - The Brains Behind Morality- Churchland, 2012 October 18; 2325; 1 box (Box 72)
    Vanuxem Lecture Patricia Churchland McCosh 10; Public Lectures
  - Global Dialogue Jeremy Adelman, 2012 November 07; 2347; 1 box (Box 73)
    Global Dialogue Series British Empire in Global Perspectives
  - Global Dialogue Jeremy Adelman, 2012 December 10; 2348; 1 box (Box 73)
    Global Dialogue Series America and the World
  - Global Dialogue Jeremy Adelman, 2012 December 02; 2349; 1 box (Box 73)
    Global Dialogue Series Anne McCauley
  - Emergency Broadcast Tower Training, 2012 December 19; 2284; 1 box (Box 71)
    P2-HD
    Emergency Broadcast Tower Training
  - Election 2012: What Does It Mean for the Internet?, 2012 November 08; 2285; 1 box (Box 71)
    Gigi B. Sohn
  - Illuminating the History of the Universe with the Cosmic Microwave Background, 2012 December 11; 2286; 1 box (Box 71)